Dear Hiring Manager,

I have been working towards a transition into software development over the last year, and was wondering if the Brio team is open to a non-student intern? I have significant experience working in a professional office environment with small teams as well as working with clients.

I've listed my Github account on my attached resume to demonstrate some basic skills with HTML, CSS, and Javascript. The first is a basic homepage with a function that calls a random background color every 3 seconds. The second is a simple counter that starts/stops with a button function.

My goal with interning is to gain experience working in a production environment with seasoned developers where I can be trained and prepared for a junior developer position (ideally at Brio!).

In addition to interning, I am willing to help with office/admin tasks if needed that are related to my previous experience.

Schedule Availability: 20 hrs / wk on site, can work additional hours as needed.

I look forward to speaking with you more about this opportunity.

Thank you,

Aaron Peazzoni

AARON PEAZZONI

Sellersville, PA, 18960 484-222-1066 peazzoni@yahoo.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2014-2015 (Nov-Present) Operations Lead, White Whale Mixers LLC, Remote - Current Part-Time

- Operations position with customer-facing responsibility that includes managing third-party logistics, design firm vendor and wholesale customers.
- Manage product roll-out with customers using enterprise applications for several national accounts.

2013-2014 (1 year) Accounting & Tax Planning Analysis, Kregel & Company CPA, Souderton PA

- Conducted financial forecasting and planning for clients to minimize tax exposure.
- Performed financial and business data conversions to cloud-based accounting platforms.
- Ad hoc accounting services including: Financial reports, Payroll, Bookkeeping, A/R & A/P.

2007-2013 (7 years) Operations Manager, One Village Coffee, Souderton PA

- Prepared annual budget, develop P/L forecasts, and manage company cash flow.
- Generated monthly financial, sales and ad hoc project reports.
- Improved supply chain processes with vendors, production team and customers that resulted in reduced operating costs by 20%.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages (Coursework/Basic Proficiency): Java, Javascript, JQuery, HTML.
- Microsoft Office strong Excel skills.
- Platform Experience: Salesforce, Wordpress, Squarespace, Xero Accounting, Quickbooks.

Github: https://github.com/peazzoni1/Projects-

EDUCATION

Villanova University
M.B.A. Program, Info. Sci. track, 2012-Present
Villanova University
M.A. Religion, 2006
Eastern University
B.A. Analytical Philosophy, 2002